# Sayan Sarkar

**Full Stack Developer** 

Email: sayan.sarkar.acme@gmail.com

Contact No.: +91 7003351006

**Location: Kolkata** 

## **SKILLS:**

- JAVA 8
- J2EE
- SQL
- SPRING BOOT
- SPRING MVC
- SPRING DATA
- REACT JS, REDUX
- JSF
- RICHFACES
- PRIMEFACES
- JAVASCRIPT
- TYPESCRIPT
- HTML 5, CSS, BOOTSTRAP

#### LANGUAGE:

- ENGLISH
- HINDI
- BENGALI

2+ years of IT experience as a Developer in Application Development and Maintenance project encompassing a wide range of skill sets. Worked in Professional Services team as Solution developer providing technical consultancy and building solutions to customer from cards and payment industry.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

 Jr. Software Engineer, Cognizant Technology Solutions [06/2019 - Present]

# Tasks/Responsibilities:

- → Have experience in rewriting legacy Java application using React is.
- → Implemented Restful Web Services using Spring Boot and Spring Data JPA in PCF platform.
- → Have experience working in JSF and Primefaces.
  - INTERN, Cognizant Technology Solutions [01/2019-04/2019]
- → Completed 4 months of internship as a full stack java developer from January 2019 to April 2019.

## **EDUCATION**

 Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science and Engineering [ 2015-2019]

Future Institute of Engineering and Management CGPA 8.47

Class 12 Board Exam ISC [2015]:

Ram Mohan Mission High School

Percentage:85.25%

Class 10 Board Exam ICSE [2013]:

Ram Mohan Mission High School

Percentage:89%